networka.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Network A

The website [www.NetworkA.com](http://www.networka.com/) (“the Site”) and the related App is owned and operated by Bedrocket Media Ventures, Inc. (“Bedrocket”).

At Bedrocket, we care about your privacy as much as you do, and we are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy, including all data that we may collect concerning you. Our Privacy Policy is designed to balance our legitimate interests in collecting personal information from you to provide the best experience possible with your reasonable expectation of privacy. The policy may be revised or updated at any time, and we encourage you to come back often to ensure you are familiar with the most recent version. This Privacy Policy outlines the manner in which we may collect personal data from you, or that you provide to us, and by using the Site and/or App you agree to the use of the data that we collect as stated. Our intent is to collect the minimum amount of data that allows us to maximize our service to you and continue to provide you the best experience possible.

**What personal information does Network A collect about me?**

a. Personal information that you provide when registering as a user on the Site or App including your name, date of birth and email address as well as any other information that may be requested upon registration.

b. Details of any visits you make to the Site and App which may include, but is not limited to, any information you demographic information you input, as well as non-personally identifiable information, such as your operating system, your IP address, which web browser you are using, and the web sites you may have visited directly before or after visiting the Site via the use of Cookies.

**How does Network A use my personal information?**

a. Non-personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties to help us to introduce, develop and improve the Site, App or for other purposes, such as providing more relevant services and advertisements to users.

b. We may use your email address to contact you and send you notifications or information related to the Site and/or App. We may also use your email address for security reasons so that we can verify your identity. We will include an opt out option for you to select to discontinue email contact

c. We may at our sole discretion and without prior notice disclose users' personally identifiable information but only when we are required to do so by a court of law.

**How does Network A use third party cookies?**

Third party vendors, such as Google, use cookies for the purposes of providing tools for gathering analytics (such as Google Analytics) or for the purposes of serving and re-marketing advertising (such as Doubleclick). You have the option to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) or [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Alternatively you can opt out of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**How does Network A handle links?**

The Site and/or App may contain links to and from third party sites or the websites of our advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any Third Party site, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for such policies. You should check these policies before you submit any personal data to such Third Party Sites.

**What relationship does Network A have with third party advertisers?**

a. Bedrocket may use third-party advertising companies to target and display advertisements when you visit the Site and/or use the App. These advertising networks may use general demographic information about your visits to the Site or App to provide advertisements about goods and/or services that may be of interest to you. They may also use cookies, and other tracking technologies to help present, target and measure advertising effectiveness.

b. Certain third party individuals or organizations may be granted access to non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form as a result of agreements between our advertising partners and us.

**Is there anything else I should know?**

We may, at our sole discretion, amend, modify or change this Privacy Policy. All such changes will be placed on this page and will supersede this version of our Privacy Policy. We suggest that you check this page each time you use the Site to ensure that it still meets with your approval. You may contact us with any questions regarding our policy at [legal@bedrocket.com](mailto:legal@bedrocket.com)
